字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen.
是现今世上速度最快的人
And I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
为了阻止邪恶极速者萨维塔
In an attempt to stop the evil speedster Savitar,
我不小心闯入了未来
I was accidentally thrust into the future,
看到他杀死了我心爱的女人
and I saw him murder the woman that I love.
但是我不会再让这事发生了
But I won't let that happen.
我会尽我一切的努力来改变未来
I'm gonna do everything in my power to change the future,
而我是唯一来得及拯救她的人
and I'm the only one fast enough to keep her alive.
我就是  闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
魔法石是一切的关键
The Philosopher's Stone has been the key to everything.
所以只要毁掉魔法石  萨维塔就会永远消失
So we destroy the Stone, and Savitar is gone for good.
我们只有一个办法
There's only one thing we can do with it.
把它扔进神速力里
Throw it into the Speed Force.
我必须尽我之力来帮忙
I have to do what I can to help.
我对病危的母亲避而不见
I'm the guy who avoided his dying mother for weeks.
有很多事情需要我去弥补
I have a whole lot to make up for.
我喜欢你  朱利安
I like you, Julian,
但我怕我的超能力
but I'm also afraid of my powers
怕它们会伤害跟我亲近的人
and what they could do to anyone who gets close to me.
我不想要这些能力
I didn't ask for these powers,
就和你不想被萨维塔利用一样
just like you didn't ask to be used by Savitar.
我们一起害怕吧
I think we should be terrified together.
没问题  我们一起
Sure. Together it is.
我这么短时间能达到  这很疯狂
It's crazy how fast I've gotten in such a short time.
我需要你再加快更多
And I'm gonna need you to get a lot faster.
不是我从萨维塔手中拯救爱瑞丝  而是你
I'm not gonna save Iris from Savitar. You are.
爱瑞丝·韦斯特  你愿意嫁给我吗
Iris West, will you marry me?
欢迎来到中城
闪电侠和闪电小子
的故乡
欢迎来到中城
闪电侠
和闪电小子的故乡
沃利创造了个人的最快速度
And Wally just beat his personal best.
巴里今天让他使出了吃奶的劲
Oh, Barry's putting him through the wringer today.
什么  是巴里吗
Excuse--Barry? Excuse me?
是  我想应该是他
Yeah, I suppose it could be Barry,
或者是他的天才教练  他在这个
or it could be his genius coach, whose sole purpose
地球上的唯一目标就是挤[牛奶]出
on this Earth is milking epic greatness
他周围人的巨大潜力
from those around him.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
-也可能是因为杰西  -什么
- It could also be Jesse. - What?
拜托  沃利可不想在她女朋友面前被打败
Come on, Wally doesn't want to get beat by his girlfriend.
还有  拜托你别再
Also, please, just refrain from
把"牛奶"用作动词了
using "milk" as a verb from now on, please.
我有点头晕了
I'm getting kind of dizzy.
头晕是正常的  华莱士
You're supposed to get dizzy, Wallace!
跑这趟路线你都应该感到精疲力尽了
You're supposed to get exhausted on this route.
这是要模拟
It's supposed to simulate
你最终遇到萨维塔时
the stress that you're gonna feel
要承受的压力
when you finally confront Savitar,
所以我的建议就是  受着吧  小屁孩
so my suggestion to you is, suck it up, buttercup!
挤出巨大潜力
Milking epic greatness.
是啊  真厉害
Yeah, no kidding.
能不能淡定点  虎妈
Why don't you take it down a little, Tiger Mom?
巴里和杰西在终点了
Barry and Jesse are at the final mark.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
沃利在冲刺了
Wally's at the home stretch.
加油
Come on...
怎么样
Guys?
0.21秒
0.21 seconds.
0.21
0.21.
足够快从萨维塔手中救出爱瑞丝了
Just fast enough to save Iris from Savitar.
你做到了
You did it.
-你做到了  -我们做到了
- You did it. - We did it.
你做到了
You did it!
You did it.
你还好吗
You okay?
还好  还好
Yeah, yeah.
我只是很高兴
I'm just... happy.
我们都很高兴  沃利  真的
We all are, Wally. We all are.
闪电侠
第三季
第十五集
朱利安
Julian.
-你好  -凯特琳  你好
- Hi. How are you? It... - Caitlin, how are you?
你从机场直接过来的吗
You've come straight from the airport?
是的  是的
Yes, yes...
巴里说他有事要跟我讲
Barry said he had something to tell me.
他在吗
Is he here?
他很快就会回来  我保证
He'll be here any minute, I'm sure.
-我们进去吧  -好的  进去
- Shall we? Yeah? - Yes, we shall.
进去
We shall.
-看看谁来了  -大家好
- Look who I found. - Hey, guys.
-怎么样  -朱利安
- How are we doing? - Julian.
很高兴见到你  很高兴见到你们
It's good to see you. Good to see you all.
杰西  你不是回地球二了吗
Jesse, I thought you were heading back to Earth-2.
我决定在这待一段时间
I actually decided to stick around for a little while.
有谁知道这是怎么回事吗
Hey, does anybody know what's going on?
我办公室还有一堆文件要处理呢
I mean, I got a mountain of paperwork back at the office.
我一点也不清楚  我还打算问你呢
No, not the foggiest. I was gonna ask you.
欢迎回来  詹姆斯
Welcome home, James.
我给你倒一杯上好的茶吧
Can I brew you a proper cup of tea?
非常提神的  伙计
And a robust pick-me-up for you, mate.
不用了  回来的路上我们去了吉特
No need. We hit Jitters on the way.
-每个人都有份  -你们
- Got everybody something. - You guys are...
你们不是快来不及了吗
I thought you were on deadline.
是的
I am.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
-给你的  -给
- For you. - Here.
你们俩怎么回事
Okay. What is going on with you two?
你要来说吗
Uh, do you want to?
交给你了
This is all you.
好  开始了
Okay, here goes.
不是吧
No!
恭喜你们  太激动了
Congratulations! That's so exciting!
谢谢你  谢谢
Thank you. Thanks.
谢谢
Hey, thanks, man.
你求得美人归了  真是太棒了
You did it. This is... This is fantastic.
好样的  乔  恭喜你
Well done, Joe. Congratulations.
爸  说句话吧
Dad, say something, please.
我的宝贝女儿
My baby girl.
你已经长成一位动人的女子
You have grown into a beautiful woman.
你要嫁给我认识最好的男人[伴郎]
You're marrying the best man I know.
谢谢
Thanks.
你们俩带给我的只有欢乐
You two bring me nothing but joy.
-我真为你们感到高兴  -好
- I'm so happy for you. - Okay.
最可爱的一对  我无法...
This cuteness right here, I cannot...
恭喜
Congrats.
-谢谢  -嗯
- Thank you. - Yeah.
说到
And speaking of, um,
伴郎
best man...
我当然会做伴郎
I'll do it. Of course.
我和巴里第一次见面的时候
When Barry and I first met...
-HR  -你是说他
- H.R. - You mean him.
好吧
Okay, good.
我
I...
我会很荣幸  真的
I'd be honored. Really.
只要我能携眷出席
I mean, as long as I can get that plus-one.
因为你们知道的  我和吉普赛
'Cause, you know, me and Gypsy,
我们将会为你们在舞池里尽情狂舞
we about to tear up the dance floor for you guys.
巴里
Barry.
我能和你说两句吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
好的
Yeah, yeah.
我想要确认你听到我在里面说的话
Now, I wanted to be sure that you heard what I said in there.
我再高兴不过了
I couldn't be happier.
好的
Okay, right.
那
So...
你为什么不征求我的同意
Why didn't you ask my permission?
我和你说过那件事
I mean, I told you the story
当年我征求弗朗辛爸爸的同意
of me asking Francine's dad's permission,
有一百次吧
like, a hundred times.
至少有一百次  那是件好事
At least, yeah. And that's a great story.
但是你漏了重点
Eh, but you missed the point?
我...  我...
I... yeah, I...
我不...  我自然而然就说出来了
I don't... It was spontaneous.
我知道你会答应的  所以我想给你惊喜
I knew you'd say yes, and I wanted to surprise you.
拉夫大楼的火警响了三次
There's a three-alarm fire in the Raab building.
消防局正在疏散
Fire department is evacuating it now.
杰西忙着问戒指的事情
Jesse is a little preoccupied with the ring,
-所以只有你和我了  -好
- so it's just you and me. - Okay.
-你们还在等什么  快去  -好
- What you two waiting for? Go. - Yeah.
华莱士
Wallace...
华莱士·韦斯特
Wallace West.
沃利
Wally...
搞什么
What the hell?
沃利
Wally.
发生什么事  怎么了
What's happening? What's wrong?
他去哪了
Where'd he go?
谁
Who?
他去哪了
Where is he?
谁  谁在哪
Who? Where is who?
萨维塔
Savitar.
我没事
I feel fine.
萨维塔的思绪在干扰你
So now Savitar's mind-punking you...
天呐
Oh, boy.
这还真是永无休止啊
This never stops never stopping.
你这样有多久了  沃利
How long has this been going on, Wally?
-有一周了吧  -一周
- Like a week. - A week.
沃利  你怎么之前不说出来
Wally, why didn't you say anything before?
因为我不知道是怎么回事
Because I didn't know what this was.
我以为也许只是在我脑中
I thought that this was just maybe in my head.
我没有仔细去想  不是故意不说出来的
You know, I wasn't looking at it like I was keeping it to myself.
但你就是这么做的  沃利
That's exactly what you did, though, Wally.
你的确没有说出来
You did keep it to yourself,
而和萨维塔有关的事  我们无能为力
and with Savitar, that's not something we can do.
我们现在说的可是爱瑞丝的命
This is Iris' life we're talking about.
-我知道  -你真知道吗  沃利
- Yes, I know that. - Do you, though, Wally?
-知道  -好了
- Yes. - Uh, okay.
到目前为止...  你只看到他是吗
Until now, it was-- you only saw him, right?
是的  这是第一次有肢体上的接触
Yeah, this was the first time it was physical.
什么  他都不在那里
What-- he wasn't there!
好吗  你都没反抗他
Okay? You weren't fighting him.
他在扰乱你的思绪
He was messing with your head.
全都是你想象出来的
It was all in your mind.
我经历过  试过
I've been there. Done that.
糟糕透顶
It's miserable.
不如我扫描一下沃利的脑部
Okay, why don't I run a brain scan on Wally,
看看他所受到的影响
see if he was similarly affected
是否和朱利安被附身时的类似
to when Julian was possessed?
好的  不如就这么做吧
Yeah, that's fine. Why don't we do that?
反正沃利也不该来这里
Wally shouldn't be in here anyway.
-什么  -巴里  他知道他搞砸了
- What? - Barry, he knows he messed up.
那不是这件事的重点  你看...
That's not what this is about, okay? Look, it's...
如果萨维塔想利用朱利安那样利用沃利
If Savitar's using Wally the same way he used Julian,
我们怎么知道他没有通过沃利监控我们
how do we know he's not spying on us through Wally right now?
沃利  我们不知道这具体是怎么运作的
Wally, we don't know how this works.
我们怎么知道他不会看到听到我们
How do we know he can't see and hear everything we're doing?
你出局了
Look, you're out.
-我出局了  -很抱歉  沃利
- I'm out? - I'm sorry, Wally.
你听起来可不怎么抱歉
Yeah, you don't sound real sorry.
好了伙计们  咱们来个快速问答
All right, fellows, let's take a quick ten.
咱们还是《四个老朋友》对吧
We're all still the "Four Amigos" here, right?
什么
What?
你们这个地球上没有那部电影吗
You don't have that movie on this Earth?
我去和他谈谈
I'll go talk to him.
好  让他清醒清醒
Yeah, talk some sense into him.
好了  现在做什么
All right. So what now?
我们从未来了解到
Well, we know from the future
萨维塔从某个地方逃出来
that Savitar gets out of wherever he is,
但现在  他还是被困住  所以...
but for now, he's still trapped, so...
我要再和他谈谈
I need to talk to him again.
不  我就知道你在想这事
No, I knew you were thinking this.
我不会答应的
All right? And I won't do it.
我不想当你跟他的私人对讲机
I'm not gonna be your personal walkie-talkie to him.
各位  我们也没法做到  我们没有魔法石
Guys, we can't. We don't have the Stone.
其实我们可以
Actually, we can.
我们还有当我们接通琳达·布莱尔时
We still have Savitar's spatial frequency
留下的萨维塔空间频率
from when we plugged in Linda Blair here,
所以我想我们可以不用魔法石来通话
so I think we could work without the Stone.
朱利安  真抱歉  我们没有选择
Julian, I'm sorry, man. We don't really have a choice.
我们有的选择  我有选择
Oh, we do have a choice. I have a choice.
而我选择拒绝
And I choose to decline.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
-我们开始争吵了  -我们不能这样
- We're starting to fray. - Well, we can't. All right?
你们只要相信我就可以了
Everybody just needs to trust me.
我知道我在做什么
I know what I'm doing.
来说服我了吗
Come to talk me into it, then?
不是
No.
巴里估计是疯了  才会认为
Barry's lost his bloody mind if he thinks
我会想自愿再被  滥用
I'm gonna volunteer to be... abused again.
他只是想保护爱瑞丝
He's just trying to protect Iris.
我们都想
We all are.
但不是像那样
But...not like that.
你不想要这么做的原因  是不是...
Is the reason you don't want to do this because...
你不想让我看到
you don't want me to see it?
我只是觉得
I just think...
听到我发出他的声音  我...
Hearing his voice coming out of me, I...
那会让你很难把我看做正常...
It just makes it impossible for you to see me as a normal--
我也曾有过别人的声音从我嘴里发出
I've had somebody else's voice coming out of my mouth,
但你依然能够看到真正的我
and you were still able to see the real me.
为什么不相信我可以做到同样的事呢
How about trusting that I can do the same thing?
抱歉
Sorry.
我就想先下手了
I just wanted to do that,
以防之后你改变主意
in case you changed your mind later.
没关系的
Quite all right.
朱利安  你会没事的
Julian, you're gonna be okay.
你知道要怎么办
You know the drill.
让你的思想变空白
Just let your mind go blank.
剩下的交给我们  好吗
We'll take care of the rest. Okay?
让萨维塔再次回到驾驶席
Just let Savitar back in the driver's seat once more.
太好了  谢谢你
Brilliant. Thank you.
赶紧搞完这事吧
Let's just get this over with, yeah?
屈服于我的威严之下
Bow before my greatness.
敬畏你面前的全能者吧
Be in awe, as you are in the presence of the Almighty.
够了  别再扯这些宗教玩意了
Enough with the... religious nonsense.
你不过是个人  像我一样
You were just a man. Like me.
我和你不一样  巴里
I'm nothing like you, Barry.
你残忍  你自私
You're cruel, you're selfish.
从我的视角来看  你是个大恶棍
From my perspective, you're the big bad.
愚蠢
Stupid.
还在呢  冒牌者
Still here, pretender?
还在寻找你的定位呢吗
Still trying to find your place?
我找到了我的定位
I found my place.
我会站在这里  与这些人一起
It's standing here with these people,
与你对抗
against you.
你知道  最可悲的就是你还活着
You know, the sad thing is that you live.
你在我的怒火下幸存
You survived my wrath.
一个懦夫  这是讽刺
The coward. Irony.
你在哪里
Where are you?
你说我把你困在了未来  在哪
You said that I trapped you in the future, where?
你能想到的唯一一个地方
The only place that you could think of.
唯一你能够关住我的地方
The only place that could hold me.
你被关了多久
How long have you been imprisoned?
长到足够我发疯好几次的了
Long enough to lose my mind several times over.
只有我的决心保持着我心智健全
It's only my will that keeps me on this side of sanity.
你知道  很有趣  当我想起心智健全时
You know, it's funny, when I think of sanity,
我可不会想到萨维塔
I don't necessarily think of Savitar.
那是因为你微不足道  西斯科
Well, that's because you're small, Cisco.
你一直都是这么微不足道
You've always been small.
回波说了你能成为一个神
Reverb told you that you could have been a god.
但相反  你情愿成为一个  技术支持
But instead, you'd rather work as...tech support.
你能告诉我为什么我们是敌人吗
You want to tell me why we're enemies?
因为我们必须是
Because we had to be.
我们中只有一个可以活下来
Only one of us could live.
你以为斯旺和极速
You thought that Thawne and Zoom
是你最大的劲敌
were your biggest foes, but...
是我才对
But it's me.
一直都是我  巴里
It's always been me, Barry.
我们对你做过什么
Man, what did we ever do to you?
你们夺走了我的一切
You took everything from me!
我没想这样  乔
I never asked for any of this, Joe.
变成这样都是拜你所赐
I am only this way because of you.
你们所有人
All of you!
我们什么时候会碰面
When do we meet?
没有多久了
Not long now.
我变成我时  你在旁边
You're there when I become who I am.
你是说  因为我你才有了速度
You're saying I caused you to get your speed?
-我创造了你  -不是
- I created you? - Oh, no.
我创造了我自己  巴里
I created myself, Barry.
唯有我才能成就伟大
Only I can bring out my greatness.
你的伟大
Your greatness?
不管你在哪
Well, you're still trapped,
现在都是困兽
wherever you are,
我不知道你要怎样逃脱
and I don't know how you're gonna escape.
我们已经把魔法石给扔了
I mean, we got rid of the Philosopher's Stone.
是吗
Did we?
我比以往任何时候都接近自由
I am closer to my freedom than I have ever been.
你所走的每一步
Every step, every move that you make,
只会让我离自由更近
it only brings me nearer to it.
我只差一样东西
I only need one more thing.
你还真是喜欢自说自话
Man, do you love to hear yourself talk.
爱瑞丝  你是想表现得不害怕吗
Iris, trying to show that you're not afraid?
但我知道你怕
But I know you are.
很抱歉  你必须死
I'm sorry that you have to die.
不是你死  就是我亡
But it's you or me.
尽管你们不自量力想改变未来
And despite your feeble efforts to change the future,
你们会失败
you can't,
因为我就是未来  闪电侠
because I am the future, Flash.
巴里  你所承受的比任何人都沉重
Barry, you've had to suffer worse than anyone.
你一生都在忍受痛苦
You've endured pain your whole life.
你的母亲
Your mother,
你的父亲
your father...
相信我
Trust me,
这道坎你永远迈不过去
you'll never get over this.
好吧
Well...
怎么样
Well?
聊得愉快吧
Good chat, was it?
我不知道还敢不敢再参加一次这通灵会
I-I don't know if I can take another one of those séances.
有人和我有同感吗
Anyone else with me?
我差点就拉裤裆了
I almost filled my drawers.
好  除了萨维塔
Okay, so other than Savitar taking
那吓死人不偿命的功力上了个新台阶
scaring-the-bejeezus-out-of-us to a whole new level,
我们还知道什么
did we actually learn anything?
-肯定要有什么  -或许吧
- Please say yes. - Maybe.
当我提到魔法石的时候  他问我们
When I mentioned the Stone, he questioned whether or not
是不是真的把它给扔了
we'd really gotten rid of it.
我们扔了  扔进了神速力里
We did. We threw it into the Speed Force.
就跟扔到了外太空没两样
That's like throwing it into outer space.
也许并不是这样
Uh, maybe we didn't.
我是说  事情可能没有这么简单
I mean, maybe there's more to it.
还有一块魔法石吗
A second Stone?
也可能是我们扔的不过是魔法石的大碎片
Or maybe the Stone that we had was part of a larger piece.
不如问问那些信徒
How about the Acolytes?
也许他们知道些我们不知道的事情
Maybe they know something we don't.
-去问问那个人怎样  -克雷格吗
- Hey, what about that one guy? - Craig?
对  就是你变成冰霜时候
Yes, the Acolyte that you dropped in on
顺路拜访的那个信徒
when you went all cold?
他车上定位系统定位显示
His car's GPS has him located
在布切拉托山附近
somewhere near... Mount Buccelato.
布切拉托  离这好几英里呢
Buccelato, that's miles away.
他到那里去干什么
What--what would he be doing over there?
只有一个办法来解答了
There's one way to find out.
说说  你看到什么了
Talk to us. What do you see?
和《夺宝奇兵2》里差不多的情景
Some serious "Temple of Doom" Stuff.
他们有个盒子
They have a box.
极速之神  你的敌人将会倒下
God of Speed, soon your enemies will fall
你将再一次屹立在这地球之上
and you will rise once more on Earth.
看起来像是上次装着魔法石的那个盒子
It looks just like the last one that held the Stone.
你猜对了  巴仔
You were right, Barr.
你打算怎么办
What are you gonna do?
我要去看看里面有什么
I'm gonna go see what's in it.
你们这是在干什么呢
What exactly were you guys doing up here?
膜拜极速之神
Worshipping His Greatness.
没了这个  我们看他能跑多远
Let's see how far he gets without this.
他可比你想得远多了
He's ten steps ahead of you.
萨维塔将无法被阻止
There's no stopping Savitar.
如果我是你
If I were you...
就把婚礼提前了
I'd move up the wedding.
到目前为止  不太顺利
So far...not so good.
什么也检测不出来
Can't get any readings off of it.
跟上次的情况一样
It's the same as the last time.
你确定这不是同一个盒子吗
Are we sure this isn't the same box?
不可能啊
Well, it can't be.
我是说  我都把另一个扔进神速力了
I mean, I threw the other one into the Speed Force.
没错  但是你说那场爆炸
Yeah, but you said the explosion
把你送到了未来
sent you to the future.
也许爆炸也对盒子产生了什么影响呢
What if it did something to the box too, you know?
我不想这么说  巴里  但是
I hate to say it, Barry, but,
就我这么多年的研究经验
after all my years of research,
我从没听过或碰到过另外的盒子与魔法石
I've never heard or come across another box or Stone;
我认为这就是原来那个
I think this is it.
如果你没说错  那我们得考虑可能
If that's true, we need to consider the possibility
萨维塔拿到魔法石了
that Savitar has that Stone.
我去检查一下还有没有放射性同位素
I'm gonna check for radioactive isotopes
或重力残留
or gravimetric force residue,
要是和上次一样
'cause if it's the same as the last time--
我们就有大麻烦了
We're in big trouble.
你可以更快的  沃利  快跑
You can go faster than that, Wally. Run!
时间到
And... Time!
很好  很好  刚才那...
Yeah. Yeah. That was, uh...
好
Good.
我们还得再来一次
We need to go again.
我不懂了  我今早还能达到那个速度的
But I don't understand. I was fast enough this morning.
怎么突然之间  我就慢下来了
Now all of a sudden, I'm too slow?
你顾虑太多了  你要放下这些顾虑
You're in your head. You gotta get out of your head, man.
你只管跑  把所有事都放在一边
You gotta just run, you gotta push everything else to the side.
-我在努力  HR  我做不到  -好吧
- Yeah, I'm trying, H.R. I can't do it! - Okay.
-好吗  -好
- All right? - Okay.
好  为什么做不到
All right. Why not?
我不知道
I don't know.
我知道
I do.
你害怕了
You're afraid.
这我也完全能理解
Which is... I totally understand.
如果换了是我  我会吓个半死
I mean, if I were in your shoes, I'd be terrified.
但是你不能带着恐惧去跑  好吗
But you can't run from a place of fear, all right?
没人心存恐惧还能把事情做好
Nobody can do anything effectively coming from a place of fear.
相信我  我知道的
Trust me, I know.
萨维塔可以进入我的思维
Savitar can get inside my head.
要是他在不恰当的时候进来了怎么办
What am I supposed to do if he does that at the wrong time?
如果我能知道那晚到底发生了什么
It sure would be a lot easier if I just
也许会简单得多
knew exactly how that night went.
可不是吗
Would it ever.
你和我想到一起去了吗
Are you picking up what I'm putting down?
是啊
Uh-huh.
我们走
Let's go.
不行  我不能用震波把你带到那去
No way. I'm not gonna vibe you there
要你亲眼看着你姐姐死
for you to watch your sister die.
好吧  这样这样这样
Okay. Just-just-just--
这是在帮华莱士
Th-this is to help Wallace.
帮他弄清事情经过
To help him see what happens
这样他就能知道到时候该怎么做了
so he knows what to do in the moment.
拜托  西斯科  求你了
Come on, Cisco, please.
如果萨维塔回来了
If Savitar's coming back
我是唯一一个能救爱瑞丝的人
and I'm the only one that can save Iris,
我必须得尽一切努力确保能救得了她
I have to do everything I can to make sure that happens.
你确定你要这么做吗
And you're sure you want to do that?
因为这不是你逃避得了的事  沃利
Because this is not something you can unsee, Wally.
如果这能帮我救我姐姐  我确定
If this is gonna help me save my sister, yeah.
我必须得去看看
I have to see it.
拜托
Please.
好吧  如果你一定要看...
Okay, if you have to see it...
下来吧  请便
Come on down. Be my guest.
HR  你知道怎么用这个  对吧
H.R., you know how to work this, right?
我知道怎么用
I know how to work this, yeah.
如果有什么差池  马上要凯特琳过来
Anything goes wrong, you get Caitlin down here stat.
我知道怎么做  上次我也在这里
I know what I'm doing. I was here the last time.
我看见你是怎么做的了  我只用这样
I saw what you did. All I got to do is do this.
-另外一个  -是另外一个按钮
- The other one. - It's the other button.
下次轻点  拜托  HR
Bit of a lighter touch next time, please, H.R.!
-收到  轻点碰  -这边
- Copy. Lighter touch. - This way.
不要
Don't!
就是这个了
This is it.
-好吧  -所以我要跑这么远
- Okay. - So that's the distance I need to cover.
不要这么做
Don't do this!
现在  我终于摆脱你的禁锢了
Now, finally, I am free of you!
巴里  我爱你
Barry, I love you.
不  别说这话  知道吗  你会没事的
No, don't say that, all right? You're gonna be all right.
我求你了  我求你了
Hey, I'm begging you, I'm begging you!
我求...
I'm beg...
巴里
Barry?
你输了  巴里
You lose, Barry.
不
No!
爱瑞丝
Iris?
爱瑞丝  爱瑞丝
Iris, Iris.
看
Look.
走吧
Come on.
你看见什么了
What--what'd you see?
一切顺利吗  有帮助吗
Was it good? Did that--did that help?
-有  -有吗
- Yeah. - Yeah?
帮助很大
It helped a lot.
沃利...
Wally...
为什么从来就没人听我的
Why does nobody ever listen to me?
你真是够了
You're so full of it.
-什么  -你怪我
- What? - Railing at me
没有告诉大家萨维塔的事
for not telling everyone about Savitar?
那你没有告诉大家的事呢  巴里
What about what you're not telling everyone, Barry?
你在...
What are you--
西斯科用震波把我带到未来
Cisco vibed me into the future.
我看见了事情经过
I saw what happened.
告诉我姐姐为什么你要求婚
Tell my sister why you asked her to marry you.
说啊  告诉她真正的原因  巴里
Go on, tell her the real reason, Barry.
他在说什么
What is he talking about?
巴里
Barry.
萨维塔杀了你的那晚
The night that Savitar kills you,
你手上没有带戒指
you didn't have a ring on your finger.
我们还没订婚
We weren't engaged yet.
你就想如果我们订婚了
So you thought that if we were...
就可能改变未来
That it might change the future.
爱瑞丝
Iris...
爱瑞丝  等等
Iris, wait.
Iris, hey. Come on.
我爱你  好吗  我最爱的就是你
I love you, okay? I love you more than anything.
这一点从没改变  将来也不会变
That part has never changed. It never will.
巴里  就因为你圣诞节的草率决定
Barry, we moved in together after some rash decision
我们才同居
that you made at Christmas,
几周之后你就求婚了
and then a couple weeks later, you proposed.
你都没争得我爸的同意
You didn't even ask for my dad's permission.
我懂  我不明白  我只是...
I know. I don't know-- I guess I got caught--
当时很困惑  我...
I got caught up in the moment. I...
这正是我害怕的
That is exactly what I am afraid of.
爱瑞丝  求你  拜托
Iris, please, come on--
巴里  给我点时间想想
Barry, I just-- I need time to think.
你没事吧
You okay?
我很担心
I'm worried.
是  我明白
Yeah, I understand.
我总是反复想到
I keep coming back to the thought that...
一切可能都因我而起
I could be the cause of all this.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
萨维塔预言说
Savitar's prophecy.
"会有人背叛你"
"One will betray you""
你可能是引狼入室了  凯特琳
You may well have invited Judas into the group, Caitlin.
那人不是你
It's not you.
这很难说
It's impossible to tell
萨维塔可能控制着我
Savitar could be controlling me,and
我们谁都不会知道
none of us would know about it.
谁都不会  连我也不行
None of us, not even me.
但这次我们知道是谁
But this time, we know who it is.
怎么会
How?
因为
Because...
是我背叛了大家
I'm the one who betrayed everyone.
这个在你手上多久了
How long have you had this?
从你把盒子扔进神速力之后
Ever since you threw the box into the Speed Force.
这只是很小一块
It's such a small piece.
我觉得不会有问题的
I didn't think it would really matter.
你为什么会冒这个险
Why would you even risk it?
因为
Because...
我以为能用它摆脱我的超能力
I thought I could use it to get rid of my powers.
那摆脱了吗
And...can you?
不知道  我还没弄懂怎么使用它
I don't know. I haven't been able to figure out how to use it yet.
好了  听着各位  我想大家都同意
Okay, well, look, gang, I think we can all agree
从另一面来看这事很简单
that this is a simple case of the other side--
凯特琳冰霜杀手的一面
Killer Frost side of Caitlin
影响她做出更好的判断  那么
clouding her better judgment, so...
不  HR  不是她
No, H.R. This wasn't her.
是我  我真的很抱歉  各位
It was me. I'm really sorry, guys.
现在  我们只需找到萨维塔在哪
Right now, we just need to figure out where Savitar is.
对  我想这计划棒极了
Yes, I think that's a fantastic plan.
我们怎么才能找到他
How are we gonna do that?
-不  -再来一次
- No. - One more time.
-不  -不不
- No. - No, no.
你想再次召唤萨维塔
You want to summon Savitar again?
我不是移动的占卜板  巴里
I am not a human Ouija board, Barry.
-你不能一直  -最后一次  好吗
- You can't just keep-- - It's the last time, all right?
只需要持续到
And only long enough to see
看我们能不能追踪他的位置
if maybe we can track his location.
-有可能吗  -不不
- Is that possible? - No. No.
朱利安  为了大家我们必须了结这事
Julian, we gotta end this, for everybody's sake.
咱们楼下见
I'll see you downstairs.
好了  你们别算上我了吧
Okay, well, you guys can count me out, all right?
因为我没带那么多装箱工到这个地球来
'Cause I didn't bring an endless supply of boxers to this planet.
朱利安  求你
Julian, please.
我本该告诉你的
I should have told you.
没想到你竟然留着魔法石的碎块
I can't believe that you would keep part of that Stone.
你不记得萨维塔让我用它干什么了吗
Do you not remember what Savitar had me do with that?
我记得
Yes, I do.
但你不在乎  对吧
But you're not concerned, are you?
你只想让你的私人超能力者专家
You just want your own personal meta-human specialist
想办法给你找到解药
to try and find you a cure.
朱利安  我不想要这些超能力
Julian, I don't want these powers.
我的余生不能拿来担心
I can't spend the rest of my life wondering
我会不会或是何时会失败
if or when I'm gonna lose this battle
最终成为冰霜杀手
and become Killer Frost.
我还以为你最明白个中滋味
I thought you more than anyone would understand that.
你知道我明白什么吗
You know-- you know what I understand?
我明白你邀我加入团队的真正原因
I understand the real reason that you invited me on this team.
不只是因为这个
That's not the only reason.
对  真希望我能相信
Yeah, I wish I could believe that.
爸爸
Dad.
我听说发生什么了
I heard what happened.
想到你可能需要喝点东西提神
Thought you might need a pick-me-up.
你小的时候百试百灵
Worked like a charm when you were a kid.
小问题的时候可以
Smaller problems.
对
Yeah.
那么
So...
你想聊聊吗
You wanna talk about it?
我不知道自己想要什么  爸爸
I don't know what I want, Dad.
爱瑞丝
Iris...
不管你现在怎么想巴里
Whatever you may be feeling right now about Barry,
那小子确实爱你
that man does love you.
这种爱很难得
That--that kind of love is rare.
爸  我也希望能这么简单
Dad, I wish it were that simple.
简单
Simple.
听着  只有你
Look, only you know
知道什么对自己好
what's good for you.
但是你们俩过的
But with the kind of lives
这种生活
that you two have,
你们两个之间的爱
that love between the two of you,
是唯一需要
that is the one thing
保持简单的事情
that should stay simple.
宝贝女儿
Baby girl.
如果你需要什么我们就在这里
We'll be here if you need anything.
好的
Okay.
又来崇拜我了吗
Back to worship me once again?
我们只想让你知道我们会打败你的
We just wanted to let you know that we're gonna defeat you.
未必
Unlikely.
你告诉我们你被
You told us that you're trapped,
永远囚禁
imprisoned for all eternity.
你永远不会逃出
You're never getting out
未来的我囚禁你的地方
of wherever my future self locked you up.
你再也不会自由
You'll never know freedom again.
中城
很快一切便会揭晓  闪电侠
All will be revealed soon, Flash.
你会感受到我的愤怒
You will face my wrath.
你会祈求仁慈
You will beg for mercy,
而你什么也得不到
and you will get none.
-有用吗  -有用吗
- Did it work? - Did it work?
是的  有个线索
Yeah. We got a hit.
只是线索是整座中城
It's just that that hit is all of Central City.
这不是线索  整个中城
That's not a hit. The whole city?
-是的  -天  好吧
- Yeah. - God. Well...
能再具体一点吗
Can we get a little more specific?
至少确定一个地点  有吗
Pinpoint a location at least-- uh, something?
也许我们能得到更具体的信息
I think maybe we can get a little bit more precise,
但是我得试下以前追踪超能力者的办法
but I'm gonna have to give it the old meta-human try.
好的
Okay.
是爱瑞丝  好吧
It's Iris. All right.
我很快回来  但是
I'll be right back, but...
如果你有什么消息就告诉我  好吗
Just let me know if you get anything, all right?
好的
All right
你要去哪里吗
You going somewhere?
是啊  我只是想回尖端科研实验室训练
Yeah, I just wanna get back to S.T.A.R. Labs and train.
鉴于你在大伙面前朝巴里发脾气吗
Seeing as how you exploded on Barry in front of everyone,
还是等等吧
might want to wait on it.
真话必须说出来
Well, the truth had to come out, so...
是的
Yeah, it did.
但最好不是这种方式
Just maybe not that way.
我们都得互相帮助
I mean, we all have to help each other,
而不是指责
not point fingers.
你说得对
You're right. I...
我会和他们讲和的  只是
I'll make it up to them. It's just,
整件事在搅乱我的脑子
this whole thing is messing with my head.
-别这样  -你不懂  杰西
- Don't let it. - You don't get it, Jesse.
你得到超能力时
When you got your powers,
你只是在街上走着
you were walking down the street.
我呢  我接触了魔法石
Me? I touched the Philosopher's Stone,
我被困在茧里  而且
I got trapped in some cocoon, and...
我只是想  因为所有这些  我...
I just feel, because of all of that, I...
我有不对劲的地方
There's something wrong with me.
我觉得萨维塔以某种方式控制我
I feel like Savitar has some kind of...hold on me.
听着  我明白
Look, I know.
好吗  但是你很坚强  沃利
Okay? But you're strong, Wally.
你可以战胜它
You can fight this.
你知道我最想要的就是拥有超能力
You know, all I ever wanted was to have powers.
做些善事
To do some good.
但是现在  我是那个要负责
But now, now I'm-- I'm the one responsible
救爱瑞丝的人
for saving Iris' life.
我不知道我能否快到可以救她
I don't know if I'm gonna be fast enough to save her, so--
好了  沃利  你并不孤单
Okay, Wally. You're not alone.
好的
Okay.
她说得对  沃利
She's right, Wally.
你并不孤单
You're not alone.
妈
Mom.
你从不孤单  沃利
You're never alone, Wally.
-我好想你  -我也想你
- I've missed you so much. - I missed you too.
沃利
Wally?
我为你感到骄傲
I'm so proud of you.
为你努力成为的人骄傲
Of what you're trying to become.
这是我想要的
That's all I want.
我只想要你为我骄傲
I just want you to be proud of me.
沃利  你真的把我吓坏了
Wally, you're really freaking me out.
我很骄傲  儿子  非常骄傲
I am, son. I'm so very, very proud.
但是你得停下来
But you have to stop.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
你太努力了
You're working so hard.
你不明白这有多危险
You don't see how dangerous it is.
儿子  你不够快
Son, you're not fast enough.
永远不会
You never will be.
但是我不能停  我必须要救爱瑞丝
But I can't--I can't stop. I have to save Iris.
-我必须  -沃利
- I have to. - Wally.
你又在我脑子里了
You're in my head again.
你总是太聪明
You were always so smart.
是吧  华莱士
Weren't you, Wallace?
但是还不够聪明
But not smart enough.
我有逃出地狱的东西  华莱士
I have what I need to escape my hell, Wallace.
不  不是所有
No, not everything.
我们还有魔法石的一部分
We still have a piece of that Stone.
暂时而已
Not for long.
而一旦我拿到后  你和你所有爱的人
And once I have it, you and everyone you love
将会消失
will perish.
沃利
Wally?
我得走了  我不能让他出去
I have to go. I can't let him get out.
-你在说什么  -萨维塔
- What are you talking about? - Savitar.
你要告诉巴里  好吧
You need to tell Barry, okay?
不  我自己可以解决
No. I can do this by myself.
杰西  拜托在这里等我
Jesse, please, just wait here.
我收到了你的留言
I got your message.
先坐下来
Yeah. Come, sit down.
爱瑞丝
Iris,
我知道你生气  但是
I know you're mad, but--
不  巴里  不是这件事
No, Barry, that's not it.
你要听我说  好吧
I just want you to listen. Okay?
你得让我说出心里话
I need you to let me say what I need to say.
好的
Okay.
我不是  生你的气
I'm not angry... at you.
我明白你
I understand that you...
你想要保护我
You want to keep me safe,
我们订婚可以改变未来
and us getting engaged could change the future.
我都明白
I-- I get all of that.
巴里  你和我求婚时
Barry, when you proposed to me...
我答应了是因为
I said yes because...
我爱你胜过其他一切
I love you more than anything.
我想成为你的妻子
And I want to be your wife.
但我以为你向我求婚完全是出于爱
But I thought that you were asking me purely out of love,
而不是恐惧
not fear.
巴里  不管你有没有意识到
And, Barry, whether you realize it or not,
我们的一部分总会是有污点的
now there's always gonna be a part of us that's tainted.
爱瑞丝  我是想救你
Iris, I'm trying to save your life.
我知道  问题就在这里
I know, and that's the problem.
我想成为你的妻子  巴里
I want to be your wife, Barry.
我不想成为
I don't want to be...
你永生需要救的
someone that you're trying to save
某个人
for the rest of eternity.
永生
Eternity.
-什么也看不到  -给我吧
- Can't see anything. - Give me those.
-这东西还有用吗  -是的
- Are those things even working? - Yep.
-住手  -我想看看
- Stop it! - I just wanna see
-它坏没坏  -你在做什么
- if they're working. - What are you doing?
-你看到什么了  -我看到白色的
- What do you see? - I'm seeing these white...
-闪光  就像  -闪光
- flashes, it's like... - Flashes?
对  就像萨维塔加速经过一样  像风暴
Yeah, it's like Savitar speeding through, like, a storm.
不是风暴
No, it's not a storm.
是神速力
It's the Speed Force.
他在神速力里
He's in the Speed Force.
所以只有极速者能够看到他
That's why only speedsters were able to see him.
萨维塔为什么要藏在神速力里
Why is Savitar hiding in the Speed Force?
不是藏
He's not hiding.
那就是你未来把他困住的地方
That's where the future you trapped him.
没错
That's right.
所以萨维塔每次
And that's why Savitar only appears
只出现一会  因为神速力
for a few moments at a time, because the Speed Force
把他吸回去了  有道理
just sucks him back in. That makes sense.
但我们把魔法石
But we threw the Philosopher's Stone
扔到了神速力里
into the Speed Force.
我们恰好给了他可以用来逃脱的东西
And we gave him the very thing he needed to escape.
但他说了  他还需要一样东西
Except, he said he still needed one thing.
我认为他无法出来
I don't think he can come out
因为他没有完整的魔法石
because he doesn't have the whole Stone.
大伙
Guys...
-沃利去追萨维塔了  -什么
- Wally went after Savitar. - What?
他开始产生幻觉了
He started hallucinating.
他觉得和他说话的是他妈妈
He thought he was talking to his mom.
不  那不是  那是萨维塔
No, that's--that's not her. That's Savitar.
-他去哪了  -我不知道
- Where'd he go? - I don't know.
他急坏了  他说
Okay. He was freaking out. He said that
他要阻止萨维塔出来
he needed to stop Savitar from getting out,
然后他就冲出去了
and he sped off.
魔法石
The Stone.
不见了
It's gone?
-不见了  -巴里  我们得找到沃利
- It's gone. - Barry, we gotta find Wally.
对  如果萨维塔拿到完整的魔法石
Yeah. If Savitar gets ahold of the Stone, then--
他一定会逃出去
He'll escape for sure.
我找不到他  他关了衣服上的遥感
I can't find him. He turned off the suit's telemetry.
拜托
Oh, come on!
可怜的华莱士
Poor Wallace.
连门都打不开
Can't even open a portal.
你无法毁掉魔法石  华莱士
You can't get rid of that Stone, Wallace.
就像你无法除掉我
Like you can't get rid of me.
闭嘴  闭嘴
Shut up, shut up.
你知道这是真的
You know it's true.
你的速度还不够快  无法靠自己把它扔进
You're not fast enough to throw it into the Speed Force
-神速力里  -闭嘴
- by yourself. - Shut up!
我要出来了  华莱士
I'm going to get out of here, Wallace.
然后我就会来找你
And then I'm gonna come for you...
巴里  还有你姐姐
and Barry and your sister,
我会杀掉所有你爱的人
and I'll kill everyone you love.
不  你不是真的
No, you're not real!
你只是在我脑海里
You're just in my head, just...
我是真的
Oh, I'm real,
我还知道你速度的局限
and I know the limits of your speed.
毕竟这是我赋予你的
After all, I'm the one who gave it to you.
至于那一点
And that...
赋予我速度
giving me speed...
是你犯下的最大的错误
that was your biggest mistake.
-出现了一个巨大的能量波动  -哪里
- There's a massive power surge. - Where?
旧柯布工厂
The old Kob Factory.
正在调出监控录像
Pulling up security footage.
天哪
Oh, my God.
沃利
Wally.
不  救救我  巴里
No! Help me, Barry!
我自由了
I am free!
大地  空气
Ground. Air...
我又能触摸到了  我又可以呼吸了
I can feel again. I can breathe again.
我终于打败了你
I've beaten you, finally.
沃利在哪
Where's Wally?
你刚对他做了什么
What just happened to him?
就如同希腊神话中的阿特拉斯一样
Like the Greek myth of Atlas,
在有人取代他之前他不能放下背上的苍穹
who could not put down the sky until someone took his place,
沃利取代了我在神速力中的位置
Wally has taken my place in the Speed Force.
你知道我的  我很喜欢这种美好的神话故事
You know me. I love a good myth.
他取代了你的位置  什么
He took your place. What...
你创造闪点之时
When you created Flashpoint,
无意中为我的回归提供了途径
you unwittingly provided me with the means for my return.
沃利
Wally...
你让我想到了把沃利变成闪电小子这个方法
You gave me the idea to turn Wally into Kid Flash,
让他变得足够快以取代我
to make him fast enough to replace me
在你打造的牢笼中的位置
in your prison.
他的年少无知和轻狂帮了我大忙
His youth and ego were my allies.
他被名利和速度所吸引
So taken with his fame and speed,
完全没有发觉自己正奔向我的陷阱
he never saw he was running right into my trap.
我要如何把他救出来
How do I get him out?
沃利已经被带走了
Wally's gone.
我要如何把他救出来
How do I get him out?
在无尽的虚空之中永恒地承受着折磨
Suffering in an endless void for all eternity.
又一位巴里·艾伦没能拯救的牺牲品
Another victim Barry Allen failed to save.
不
No!
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you!
如果你有能力终结我的生命
If you had the strength to end my life,
你早就在未来这么做了
you would have done it in the future.
但巴里·艾伦未能痛下杀手  他是个好人
But Barry Allen doesn't kill. He's the good guy.
乔抚养成人的男孩  爱瑞丝心爱的男人
The boy Joe raised. The man Iris loves.
你拥有一切
You have everything.
但同时也不配拥有一切
And deserve none of it.
我要像我在未来已经做过的那样毁了这座城市
I'm going to destroy this city like I did in the future,
这样你就可以看清真相了  巴里
so you can see the truth, Barry.
然后  你会把我当成神一样膜拜
And then, you'll treat me like a god.
你根本不是神
You're not a God!
你是谁
Who are you?
我就是未来  闪电侠
I am the future, Flash.
露出你的真面目
Show your face.
我是如此强烈的想杀了你
I want so badly to kill you,
我也会这么做的
and I will.
但你必须得多活一会
But you have to live a little while longer.
活到亲眼看着爱瑞丝死去
Long enough to see Iris die.
刀刃没有伤到你的内脏
The blade didn't hit your organs,
但它击碎了你的锁骨
but it did shatter your clavicle.
忍耐一下  伙计  忍住
Hang in there, man, hang in there.
-我们得把刀刃拔出来  -拔吧
- We have to take it out. - Do it!
你的新陈代谢系统
Any medicine I give you
会迅速消耗掉我给你用的任何药物
your metabolism will burn through.
好的  直接拔  好吗
All right. Just do it, okay?
-就直接拔出来  -把他按住
- Just do it. - Hold him down.
-好了  -你会没事的  伙计
- Okay. - Gonna be okay, mate.
-你会没事的  -咬住这个
- You're gonna be okay. - Bite down on this.
抱歉  对不住了
I'm so sorry.
三  二  一
Three, two, one.
-我昏迷了多久  -没多久
- How long was I out? - Not long.
你现在感觉很疼吗
Are you in much pain?
我也许能从这刀刃中查到点什么线索
I might be able to do something with this.
乔
Joe.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这不怪你
Not your fault.
他在哪里
Where is he?
我是说  他在受苦吗  还是
I mean, is he in pain? Is he...
将面临比死亡更可怕的命运
One will suffer a fate worse than death.
杰西  我
Jesse, I...
我并不是你父亲  我真的不
I'm not like your dad. I don't really...
不知道现在该说什么话
know what the right words are--
我们下面怎么办
What are we gonna do?
我们必须把他救回来  我们必须得去救他
We have to bring him back. We have to save him...
我不能失去沃利  巴里
I can't lose Wally, Barry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我去研究研究这个刀刃
I'm gonna work on this.
我也先走了  回头见
Yeah. I'll see you soon.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我就不该
I should have never...
-我当时很害怕  -我知道
- I was afraid. - I know.
相信我  我知道
Believe me, I know.
恐惧会驱使我们做很多我们不应该做的事
Fear makes us do a lot of things that we shouldn't.
我的恐惧是造成这一切的根源
My fear's the reason for all of this.